Class of 1975 Records, 1971-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1975 Records
1971-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1975.
RG 80 UUID:69f86f1e-9fc7-4b9b-a3a6-a0135971f82f
3 boxes (1 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1975.
The Class of 1975 was the ninety-seventh graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1975 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1975, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1975 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- General 1971-1975 (Box 2260, Folder 1)
- General-Women's Liberation 1971 (Box 2260, Folder 2)
- Commencement 1975 (Box 2260, Folder 3)
- Commencement Photographs 1975 (Box 2260, Folder 4)
- Commencement Speaker 1975 (Box 2260, Folder 5)
- Freshman Handbook 1971 (Box 2260, Folder 6)
- Groups 1971-1975 (Box 2260, Folder 7)
- Ivy Day 1975 (Box 2260, Folder 8)
- Last Chapel 1975 (Box 2260, Folder 9)
- Class Letters 1975-1977, 1984 (Box 2260, Folder 10)
- Class List 1974 (Box 2260, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1980 (Box 2260, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1985 (Box 2260, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1990 (Box 2260, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1995 (Box 2260, Folder 15)
- Reunions 2000 (Box 2260, Folder 16)
- Reunions-Reunion Book 2000 (Box 2260, Folder 17)
- Reunions 2005 (Box 2260, Folder 18)
- Reunions 2005 (Box 2260, Folder 19)